[Music] It has happened
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to Option Gyan channel,
friends,
I have installed the thing of position stock, whose name
is World MP,
you people have to back this stock around the current rate i.e.
posted rate and
wish by depositing around 1250,
if the stock consolidates below 1250 for three-four days, reaches
1250 but is
not able to cross above it, then you people
will unite, this is only for those friends who are
position traders, position to friends are those
who buy and wash their stock today,
I fold it, sometimes I fold it for 5 minutes,
they do
not do it more than this and if they
get 30% return BCCI, then they book their profit, so
if you want to invest
in the stock, then
you should keep a target of at least three-four years for more than one year, for adjustment of one year's fit,
investment
points, that emphasis, so if you are an investor and
want to invest, then whichever
stock I give  Friends, its fundamentals are very
good, so if you
invest in it, you will see very good returns in four-five years,
but whenever it goes into stop loss,
you have to wish there, keep buying the stock, do
not panic, friends,
whenever there is panic in the market, you
people are not positive to buy there,
you will be able to buy only if you have
not invested all your capital in the market, so that is
why I always say that
bring 50% of your capital, you must have seen
that earlier when there was panic, people used to get very
scared, but at the time of combination
in March, when panic came, there people invested
money by filling it in good stocks, from the
present people were asked to invest, then I will
show you that the market did not get affected,
here people talked about investing and the market was
trying to lose its condition, so the
mentality of people has changed now,
whenever panic comes in the market, people invest money, so
you people also, whenever you get the first chance,
you invest the money, take the entire money together in the
market and tell me your
money.  Use it in mutual funds etc. as well
so that whenever there is a dip in the market,
you people edit your mutual funds here and
put your money in the market.
Friends, I
want to discuss this topic with you about the fundamentals as well. You should
also look at its fundamentals once.
Yes, it is definitely
visible to the people in the app itself. You have to go to the fundamentals in it.
The company manufactures heavy electrical
equipment. If you
click on the fundamentals, it will take
you to the checklist.
Here they have given the investment checklist,
note that you people can
see the points in the checklist. Out of 5, you will
see the chart market here
and the dividend return of Jaypee company is
good. Friends, I consider it for my long
term. This is my
own criteria. You
can see the app lock as per your understanding. You can like right here as per what you people understand. If we
talk about the pencil stand of the company, then it is
in 2020
where people were growing with money and Corbett.  The
company has increased its revenue and
along with the increase, the
company's profit has also increased.
Within six months in 2021, the company has made its
profit more than last year,
that too is less, but the revenue is of great concern.
If the company performs well in the next six months, then
it will become a very
good profit in the last. If we
talk about the financial statement, friends, the
company's profit statement itself is
tremendous. The company has doubled its market share within 5 years.
Where the company's
market share was 1.03 percent, it has
changed to 2.5 percent in 5 years. The company's
revenue growth is also
much better than the industry's revenue growth.
Where the industry's revenue
growth is
-80 percent, there was a time peak
when the demand was 5.27 percent. Now you people
can understand how fundamentally
strong the company is and if you are
getting the stock near 2011, then you people should
consider the stock in your portfolio. So
friends, if you like this  If you like the video then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe.
Thank you for watching my video.